products-placement.com 2013-10-30

# Privacy Policy - Products-placement.com

### Privacy Policy

**_Last Updated: 11/10/2012._**

Escolade Solutions LTD is committed to safeguard the privacy of its customers and individuals who make use of our online facilities. This policy provides you with information about what data we collect and how this data is processed by us. 

#### Collection and use of information

In general, you can visit the Escolade Solutions LTD website (the 'Website') without telling us who you are or giving any personal information about you. Information which you provide may be used: 

  * to fulfil your requests for our products or services,
  * to fulfil the purpose for which you provided the information,
  * for customer service purposes,
  * for marketing and promotional purposes,
  * to conduct research,
  * to provide information that we believe may be of interest to you,
  * to enforce the legal terms that govern your use of our Website, and/or for the reasons specific to the type of collection of information. We may also collect and store certain types of data as described in more detail below.

**Cookies and Web Beacons** \- When you visit our Website, we or our service providers, advertisers or partners, may send one or more cookies to your computer or use web beacons to improve the quality of our service by analyzing traffic pattern, tracking user trends and conducting optional research surveys. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your browser and a web beacon is a single pixel or clear GIF which are small pieces of code placed on a web page. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies and similar technologies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Web beacons may also be disabled by disabling JavaScript on your computer. However, alteration of such settings may affect the functionality of our website. 

**Log information** \- When you visit our Website, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies as explained above. 

**Google Analytics** web analytics service - We use Google Analytics web analytics services on our Website. Google Analytics may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as any text you type in this website. Neither we nor Google Analytics collect any personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter in this website and we mark certain "sensitive" visitor fields (such as fields where financial information is inputted) in a special way so that such information will not be transmitted, stored and processed by the Clicktale service. 

**Electronic notices** \- We may provide you with information and notices regarding the **Escolade Solutions LTD** products, surveys or other information which may be of use or interest to You, via the email address you designate in the payment process or when you sign up for our newsletter. We may also follow up on an abandoned shopping cart to see if there was a problem with your use of our website. You may withdraw your consent for promotional or retargeting emails at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of each notice sent. We may also send you transactional, technical or other service notifications from time to time. These messages are sent only to individuals who have purchased our products or services and are essential to maintain the functionality of same, so there is no opt-out available for this type of notifications. 

**Escolade Solutions LTD Products** \- Whilst in use, the **Escolade Solutions LTD** product may collect some information from your computer (e.g. frequency of use, system name, windows version and browser type, IP address, installed devices and date of installation). We will only use this information to improve our products and services. When you purchase a **Escolade Solutions LTD** product from this website, you will be required to provide personal information (including your credit card details) to our trusted billing merchant. Information you provide to our billing merchant will be processed in accordance with its privacy policy and you are therefore advised to review such policy prior to purchase. **Escolade Solutions LTD** will have access to all details on the purchase, excluding your credit card or other payment details, for authentication of license, statistical, notification and support related services. You may also access your purchase details remotely by submitting a request on our Support Website. 

#### Information sharing

**Escolade Solutions LTD** will only use your personal information for the purposes which are specified in this policy. We may engage third party service providers that assist us in providing or improving our services as explained above and we might need to share some personal or other data with them to enable them to do so. These service providers are either subject to this privacy policy or follow practices that offer an equivalent level of protection and may be located outside the EU, in countries where an adequate level of protection is ensured. We will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your consent. 

#### Information processing and security

products-placement.com processes personal information in Belize. Information is retained on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data held by us. 

#### Data integrity

We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. You are therefore kindly requested to inform us of any change referring to your personal data held by us. You have the right to access the personal information that we may hold about you, to rectify this data or object to the storage of the data for legitimate purposes by contacting us at <http://products-placement.com/contact>

#### Privacy of business partners

Our website and our newsletter may include various links to third party websites or promote third party products. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties in any way. We strongly suggest that you refer to the their privacy policy before accessing any website or making any purchase so that you are aware of the applicable practices and thus be able to make an informed decision about your actions and/or transactions. 

#### Children

This Website is not aimed at children and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children. Minors should not use this Website unless supervised by an adult. 

#### Changes to this policy

Please note that this policy may change from time to time. All updates will be published at this site and, if the changes are significant, the changes will be posted on this page thirty days prior to taking effect. Each version of this policy will be identifiable at the top of this document by its effective date. We encourage you to refer to this policy periodically.
